But in the end, everyone stopped but a few.
There were a few who moved back to Sinai.
Most others, most of the strength, which was over 240 men -
—The elected to stay in Lebanon and complete the assignment -
- which was to prepare for other nations that took over.
We do not see any rescue workers, there is no clearing ...
... is also a show of the very latest in Russian military technology ...
... the militia Maap's closest roadblock ...
... this tape -moving artillery piece ...
... there a child was killed and another seven people were injured.
After Lebanon, I decided.
One of the reasons was precisely that I met many foreign correspondents -
When we round a mountain bump, there are three masked men -
- With dark clothes and masks and aims at my face and tries to stop us.
But we had already discussed conceivable scenarios and agreed -
- If we would drive and then you push into the car from behind.
The rear window disappears, it turns some bullets into the plate -
- And I feel I have been met.
But it is a superficial injury.
It goes outside the ribs, and eventually gets stuck in the arm.
When traveling in this type of area -
- Conflict or disaster areas, so I think it's partly the same type-
–As people who are drawn to these areas because they want to make an effort -
- And they want to be where they really affect.
–And even soldiers who go out to make a mission-
- Therefore, you think you can do useful.
"Today during the morning Karlsson and I go into a burial ground and look."
"All graves are shredded or broken."
"The graves are plundered."
"Many chests are opened and the corpses are completely visible."
"We photograph and leave."
It has certainly shaped me a lot as a human being, the experiences -
- And you learn a lot about yourself when you end up in stressful situations.
Then you are put to the test and learn a lot about yourself.
So it was definitely an effect of that service.